For many of us, sandwiches are something simple.
对我们许多人来说，三明治是很简单的东西。
Something we can take to work or school to avoid having to cook lunch, something we can buy quickly and cheaply.
我们可以带去上班或上学，而不需要做午餐，又快速、又便宜。
For many of us, we don't even need to stop working to eat them.
对我们许多人来说，我们甚至不需要停下工作来吃它们。
Sandwiches could possibly be the ultimate convenience food.
三明治可能是终极的方便食品。
But now it seems people are realising that the humble sandwich can be so much more.
但现在，人们似乎意识到，不起眼的三明治可以远不止如此。
There's nothing convenient about waiting an hour and paying five times the price of a supermarket sarnie, but that's exactly what customers at one London sandwich shop have been doing.
等待一个小时并支付超市三明治五倍的价格，可一点也不方便，但这正是一家伦敦三明治店的顾客们一直在做的事情。
What is it that makes people so keen to get their hands on these £12 sandwiches?
是什么让人们如此渴望得到这些12英镑的三明治呢？
Firstly, it's the ingredients.
首先是食材。
As baking has become more popular, good quality bread is both available and expected.
随着烘焙变得越来越流行，人们期待买到优质面包。
The brains behind many of these gourmet sandwich shops are often people who have worked in the kitchens of top, Michelin-starred restaurants.
许多这类美食三明治店背后的策划者，往往是曾在顶级米其林星级餐厅厨房工作过的人。
This means that they bring a fine-dining attitude to their sandwiches, sourcing the best and freshest ingredients, combining them in new and creative ways.
这意味着他们将精致餐饮的态度带入三明治，以新颖和创造性的方式将采购来的最优质、最新鲜的食材组合起来。
Secondly, it's the size.
其次是尺寸。
Max Halley, owner of a similar sandwich shop, boasts that the sandwiches his shop makes are twice the size of most burgers.
一家类似三明治店的老板马克斯·哈利夸口说，他店里制作的三明治是大多数汉堡的两倍大。
Finally, having sandwiches that look both huge and delicious is perfect for social media.
最后，拥有既巨大又美味的三明治非常适合社交媒体。
While they may be more expensive than supermarket sandwiches, they are far more accessible than many other dining options.
虽然它们可能比超市三明治更贵，但比许多其他餐饮选择要容易获得得多。
Being enticing, affordable, and trendy is an almost guaranteed way to attract attention online and bring crowds to the shops' doors.
诱人、价格合理且时尚，几乎是吸引网络关注、让人们涌向店门的保证。
That's what's leading some to spend most of their lunch hour queueing up for a bite.
这就是为什么有些人会把大部分午休时间花在排队等待一口美味上。
And why not?
为什么不呢？
They might be a bit too expensive to have every day, but taking time away from your desk to eat something that has been thoughtfully prepared from fresh, high-quality ingredients isn't a bad thing.
它们可能有点太贵，不适合每天吃，但离开办公桌，花点时间享用由新鲜、优质食材精心准备的食物，并不是坏事。
It could be a good alternative to munching on industrially-produced supermarket sandwiches at your desk while staring at a spreadsheet.
与一边盯着电子表格一边在办公桌前大口咀嚼工业化生产的超市三明治相比，这可能是更好的选择。